Hey guys and welcome to the seventh and final episode of the attraction blueprint guys,
Hola a todos y bienvenidos al séptimo y último episodio de la serie "Estrategias de atracción".
this is your bonus video,
Aquí está el vídeo bonus.
this is the one that I probably enjoy talking
Este es probablemente mi tema favorito.
about the most and it is what makes an attractive man,
:¿Qué hace que un hombre sea atractivo y seductor?
what is she truly desire and crave in a man?
¿Qué es lo que realmente quiere una mujer en un hombre?
And this is something that you have to do, you have to become this man,
Y en eso es en lo que tienes que trabajar: tienes que convertirte en ese hombre.
this version of you, and it's something you have to work on,
Esa versión de ti mismo.
oh if you only knew how much I had to work on these things because...
¡Ah, si supieras cuánto trabajo tuve que poner en estas cosas porque...!
'i was ofweight my entire life, was a shy introvert,
"He tenido sobrepeso y he sido una introvertida tímida toda mi vida".
um, like i had everything against me in the world of dating,
Um, en el mundo de las citas, todo estaba en mi contra.
um, so the man you see before you today is giving you all this advice,
El hombre que te da este consejo hoy
this is from working on this for a long time and getting better at this,
Es el resultado de mucho trabajo y mejoras significativas en esta área.
um, not only like my physical parents, how i dress, um, but also how i speak,
Um, no sólo como mis padres biológicos, mi forma de vestir, um, sino también mi forma de hablar,
and these techniques i've learned through trial and error a lot of them,
y aprendí estas técnicas por ensayo y error, muchas de las cuales
um, these are all things that have been battle tested,
Han sido probados y comprobados.
and i know for fact work not only for myself,
Y sé con certeza que no sólo funcionan para mí,
but dotally through my clients as well uh, i have that evidence,
pero también, muy concretamente, para mis clientes: tengo pruebas de ello.
so today i want to talk about what makes you desirable as a man,
Hoy quiero hablarte sobre qué es lo que te hace deseable como hombre.
very first thing guys and this is probably i put this first
Lo primero, muchachos, y probablemente sea lo primero que voy a abordar, es que
because it's i don't for some reason i find the majority of guys,
No es un gran problema
this is the number one thing they ask me about because they
Y esta es la pregunta que me hacen con más frecuencia:
struggle with and it's humor guys you have to have a sense of humor,
Es difícil, y es cuestión de humor, chicos. Hay que tener sentido del humor.
you have to have that playful flirty personality,
Tienes que tener esa personalidad juguetona y seductora.
so the biggest question a lot of guys ask me
La pregunta que muchos hombres me hacen con más frecuencia es: "
is like robbie i'm not in like i was not naturally funny,
“No soy como Robbie, no soy gracioso por naturaleza”.
how do become funny?
¿Cómo llegar a ser gracioso?
how do i have more of a humorous personality?
¿Cómo puedo desarrollar una personalidad más ingeniosa?
here's the ways that did it for myself guys,
Aquí están los métodos que me funcionaron, muchachos:
i actually just started watching a ton of standup
Acabo de empezar a ver muchos monólogos cómicos.
and my favorite type of stand-up is crowdwork right,
Y mi tipo favorito de stand-up es la interacción con el público, ¿verdad?
like guys like matt rife um uh i forgot his first name but um last name is car
Chicos como Matt Reif, eh... Olvidé su nombre, pero su apellido es Craig.
um ferguson the late night host is fantastic at this um flirty
Ferguson, el presentador del programa de entrevistas, es genial en esto... eh...
humor uh craig ferguson so i started studying comics of how they're talking what
Humor coqueto, Craig Ferguson. Así que empecé a estudiar a los comediantes, su forma de hablar, ¿sabes?
what line were they using,
¿Qué chistes usaban?
what was their delivery like, what was their pitch like,
¿Cómo era su manera de hablar?
um, what was their body link was like, i started studying that, next thing you can do um,
¿Su lenguaje corporal? Estudié todo eso. Y luego... eh...
and actually i stole this um from
y lo tomé de
truman was write down like write down your favorite quotes,
Truman, puedes escribir cosas, como tus citas favoritas.
write down your favorite stories, keep dad jokes on hand right,
Escribe tus historias favoritas y mantén a mano tus chistes favoritos.
like i just keep them on hand, memorize them, it's always fun to throw those out,
Siempre los tengo a mano, los memorizo y siempre son divertidos.
always look for opportunities in the conversation of you have a funny story about that,
Busque siempre la oportunidad de contar una historia divertida en una conversación.
tell it, you have a that's what she said comment about that,
Simplemente dilo, di algo como: "Él lo dijo".
tell it guys, there's ways you can practice humor,
Chicos, hay formas de practicar el humor.
you know get around your boys more and just like have that locker room talk with them,
Ya sabes, pasar más tiempo con tus amigos y hablar con ellos, como en el vestuario.
um, yes you can memorize all of this, but you have to practice it,
Um, sí, puedes memorizar todo esto, pero tienes que practicar.
you have to practice telling dad jokes, you have to practice making smart ass comments,
Tienes que practicar contar chistes de papá, tienes que practicar hacer comentarios sarcásticos,
which is absolutely my brand of if you can't tell from our interaction so far um,
que es exactamente mi estilo, en caso de que no lo hayas notado en nuestras conversaciones anteriores...
but you have to practice telling a funny story,
pero tienes que practicar contar historias divertidas,
but you can't practice these things, just immerse yourself in humor, go to stand up,
Pero no puedes practicar realmente, sólo tienes que sumergirte en el humor, hacer comedia stand-up.
i literally went to a stand-up show last week,
De hecho fui a un espectáculo de comedia la semana pasada.
it was hilarious and i actually learned some stuff that i've been using,
Fue muy divertido e incluso aprendí un par de cosas que he estado usando desde entonces.
um, but just study it guys, study it practice, you're going to get better at it.
Um, pero aprendádlo, muchachos, aprendádlo, practicadlo, y entonces mejoraréis.
um, next thing, you have to have an adventurous life,
Entonces tendrás que vivir una vida aventurera.
you have to live adventure, you have to take risk.
Hay que vivir la aventura, hay que arriesgarse.
you have to go do fun things um when i was single probably the times of
Debes estar haciendo cosas divertidas... um, cuando estaba soltera, probablemente cuando... el período
my life where i was picking up the most women having the most successful women
de mi vida donde salí con más mujeres, las mujeres más inteligentes.
was when i was doing adventures i would go on the boat i would go you know
Esa fue la época en la que me iba de aventuras, a hacer viajes en barco, ¿sabes?
i'd go with a bunch of people and go um hiking or we'd go and like shoot guns
Salí con un grupo, fuimos de excursión, de caza.
or whatever i would just go do adventurous fun things with a group of people
o lo que sea. Estaba haciendo cosas divertidas y aventureras con un grupo de personas.
and women love being there right um so I would just live this like an adventurous life,
Y a las mujeres les gusta participar en esas cosas, ¿verdad? Así que viví esa vida aventurera.
my buddy would call me like, hey, where are we going this weekend,
Mi amigo me llamó y me preguntó: “Oye, ¿a dónde vamos este fin de semana?”
I'm like, I don't, let's find somewhere,
Y yo dije: "No sé, busquemos otra cosa".
uh, so we go take like weekend road trips and just go live life that tells a story,
Así que hicimos viajes de fin de semana por carretera y vivimos una vida de contar historias.
story that Shack she wants to read.
Historias que Shack quiere leer.
One of the biggest mistakes I see lot of guys making in today's dating
Uno de los mayores errores que veo que cometen muchos hombres en el mundo de las citas actual es este:
world is they don't live an adventurous life and they don't like those
Creen que no viven una vida aventurera y no se divierten.
stories that I I had you create an advanced communication lot of guys...
Historias que he escrito, historias a través de las cuales te he ayudado a mejorar tus habilidades de comunicación, muchos hombres...
talk to don't even have those stories, okay?
Habla con alguien que ni siquiera conozca estas historias, ¿de acuerdo?
if you don't have those stories,
Si no tienes estas historias,
you need to go make them, you need to go on some adventures,
¡Tienes que crearlos tú mismo! Vive aventuras,
go find some crazy fun things to do, go just go enjoy life,
¡Busca experiencias verdaderamente increíbles y disfruta la vida!
those are stories you talk to women about, the more you live life,
Éstas son las historias que les cuentas a las mujeres durante toda su vida.
the more interesting you are, so you have to live this adventure life guys,
¡Cuanto más interesantes seáis, más aventuras deberíais tener, chicos!
one of the things that tell lot of my younger clients is,
Muchos de mis clientes más jóvenes notan esto:
hey, right now at this point in your life, say yes, until you can't say yes anymore,
Escucha, ahora, en esta etapa de tu vida, di que sí mientras puedas.
stop being a hermit, stop being introvert,
Dejen de actuar como ermitaños, dejen de ser introvertidos,
stop sitting at home on the weekends, just go do stuff,
Deja de quedarte en casa los fines de semana: ¡sal!
you may not like it, okay, whatever, you can learn from that and not do it any?
Puede que no te guste, vale, sea lo que sea, puedes aprender de esto y no volver a hacerlo nunca más.
more, but just go do a bunch of stuff, go live an adventurous life.
Más aún: haz muchas cosas, vive una vida aventurera.
guys, we've already talked about the third thing, confidence.
Chicos, ya hemos hablado del tercer punto: la seguridad.
women deeply love confidence, why? because confidence makes a woman feel safe and secure.
A las mujeres les encanta la confianza. ¿Por qué? Porque la confianza en sí mismas les da seguridad y serenidad.
the more confident you are,
Cuanto más seguro estés,
the more you can be the other aspects of what she needs you to be,
Cuanto mejor puedas encarnar los demás aspectos que necesita.
like confidence is kind of the the foundation,
La confianza en uno mismo es, en cierto sentido, la base,
the root system of everything else that makes a man attractive.
el sistema que subyace a todo lo que hace atractivo a un hombre.
a man's not going to go into crazy adventures if he's not company, he's not going to have.
Un hombre no se embarca en aventuras locas sin compañía.
humor if he's not conf cuuse he's too scared to tell the joke um so confidence is kind
No tendrá sentido del humor si se siente inseguro porque no se atreve a contar el chiste... En resumen: la confianza en uno mismo es importante.
of the foundation which all the other tractor traits come from which lead into the
La base sobre la que se asienta
next two the fourth thing that really makes men attractive is their
Todas las demás cualidades que hacen a un hombre verdaderamente atractivo se basan en su
leadership now i will say this i'm not talking about bossing her around i'm not
Liderazgo. Cuando hablo de liderazgo, quiero dejar claro que no me refiero a dominio, no lo hago.
talking about you know this this really weird leadership that lot of men think um
¿Conoces ese extraño estilo de liderazgo en el que muchos hombres piensan...?
it is that like she's subservient to you blah blah blah and like no your job as a man
Como si fuera sumisa a ti, bla, bla, bla. No, tu rol de hombre...
is to lead and invite her to come with you like hey i'm living this amazing life i
está tomando la iniciativa e invitándola a unirse a ti, como, "¡Hola, estoy viviendo una vida increíble!
am going here you're more than welcome to come join me it's not hey you go no it's look
Voy para aquí, eres más que bienvenido a unirte a mí". No es "Oye, vamos", no, es "Mírame".
i'm leading you're more than welcome to follow and i'm inviting you to come with
Yo te guiaré, eres bienvenido a seguirme y te invito a venir conmigo.
me and you you actually when you're setting dates you lead her on that date you lead
Al momento de concertar una cita, tome la iniciativa.
her to the date by telling her where you're going um
La invitas y le dices a dónde vas...
"your job as a man is to lead right,
"Tu papel como hombre es liderar bien".
you open doors, you walk on the correct side of the sidewalk, which I know guys,
Abres las puertas, caminas por el lado derecho de la acera. Lo sé, chicos.
it's the side with the cars, not the side of the building.
Es el lado con los coches, no el del edificio.
um, I just say that I laugh about it cuz I've had so many guys ask me,
Um, me río de ello porque muchos hombres me han preguntado eso...
but you do the masculine leadership things to show her I'm in control.
pero le estás demostrando que eres tú el que está a cargo.
I've even had guys asked me this like, bro, like, why,
Algunos incluso me preguntan: “Amigo, ¿por qué?”
like, what about you makes men want to fall?"
¿Qué es lo que te atrae tanto para los hombres?
you and like how did you like why? i'm like, well
¿Tú y cómo lo hiciste? ¿Por qué? Siempre respondo: "Bueno,
i know where i'm going and i know how to get there and i'm not scared to go,
Sé a dónde voy y cómo llegar, y no tengo miedo de intentarlo.
so do it, i'm very bold and decisive in my actions, i'm very deliberate in my actions,
¡Así que inténtalo! Soy muy valiente y decidida en mis acciones, actúo con gran consideración.
and that gives other people the the security to know they can follow me.
Y esto les da a otros la confianza para seguirme.
woman will never follow the leadership of a weak man that's indecisive,
Una mujer nunca seguirá la autoridad de un hombre débil e indeciso.
that's constantly making mistakes.
que sigue cometiendo errores
that doesn't know what he wants out of life.
y no sabe qué quiere de la vida.
I heard one guy say like one of the best things
Una vez escuché a alguien decir que una de las mejores cosas
you can do as a man is you know know who you are,
Que se puedan hacer es lo que hace el hombre: conocerse a sí mismo.
which is confidence in leadership, know where you're going,
Esto incluye una actitud segura y determinación.
and then have a good time getting there, you can do those three three things,
Y disfruta del viaje. Puedes combinar todas estas cosas.
he b like that's even more simple than what I'm talking about,
Él dice que es incluso más fácil de lo que estoy hablando.
but like those three things make you super attractive as a man is when
Pero como estas tres cosas hacen a un hombre extremadamente atractivo, todo se reduce a...
you know who you are and you're comfortable and confident in that person,
Quién eres, para sentirte cómodo y seguro en
you know where you're going, you're bold and decisive in your leadership.
presencia de esa persona, conocer tu objetivo, liderar con valentía y determinación
and you have a good time getting there,
y disfruta del viaje. Exactamente,
that's that, that's that humor adventure part of it.
Esta es la parte divertida y aventurera.
um, so guys, the last component of what i want to talk about today is safety,
Bueno, muchachos, el último punto del que quería hablar hoy es la seguridad.
this one, especially in today's modern culture,
Especialmente hoy en día,
um, where we do have lot of craziness in this world, women have to feel safe with you,
Con toda la locura del mundo, las mujeres necesitan sentirse seguras contigo.
and there's a couple different levels of safety,
Y hay diferentes tipos de seguridad.
they have to feel safe like physically, safety around, you can't be creepy,
Necesitan sentirse físicamente seguros; no puedes parecer intimidante.
you can't be awkward, you can't be weird, you can't be fidgety,
No puedes ser torpe, extraño, inquieto:
and all these other weird things that see a lot of guys
todas esas otras rarezas que muchos hombres ven en ella
is doing because they haven't done the work on themselves,
Se deben a que no han trabajado sobre sí mismos.
so yes, a part of is physical safety,
Sí, la seguridad física es importante.
a part of it is, and this is you know oftenimes misconstrued is financial safety,
Otro punto importante que a menudo se malinterpreta es la seguridad financiera.
she needs to know that is if if you two have a future together,
Ella necesita saber que si tienen un futuro juntos,
you're good right, you can take care of her, um, and when it comes to money guys,
Puedes mantenerla. Y en cuanto al dinero, hombres...
like I'm tired of guys like thinking they did make a certain amount of money get the girl,
Estoy cansado de ciertos hombres que piensan que sólo porque han ganado suficiente dinero, pueden seducir a una mujer.
simply not true, I've gotten amazing women dead broad before
Está mal. He tenido sexo con mujeres increíbles.
um because I had all the other characteristics of attraction.
Um, porque tenía todas las otras cualidades atractivas.
but even the research points, it's not the money she's attracted to,
Pero los estudios también muestran que no es el dinero lo que la atrae,
it's the characteristics of the man it took to make that
pero las cualidades del hombre que lo hicieron posible.
money that she's attracted to extroversion being one of the highest.
El dinero que la atrae es su extroversión, uno de los aspectos más importantes.
um, so she's physically safe with you,
Así que se siente físicamente seguro contigo.
she knows, you're not going to hurt her and you won't let anyone else hurt her,
Ella sabe que no le harías daño y que no dejarías que nadie más le hiciera daño.
she knows - if she wants a future with you,
¿Qué es?
you can financially take care of her, and the third thing,
Puedes cubrir sus necesidades financieras si quiere un futuro contigo. En tercer lugar,
the most often overlooked thing from guys is emotional safety,
Lo que los hombres más a menudo descuidan es la seguridad emocional.
and i often don't talk about this this early in a program guys, but i need to,
No suelo abordar este aspecto tan al principio de un programa, pero tengo que hacerlo.
because i see this tripping up lot of guys,
Porque veo cuántos hombres fracasan.
so emotional safety is this: you're comfortable and okay with her emotions,
La seguridad emocional significa esto: puedes gestionar bien tus sentimientos y estás en paz con ellos.
you know, maybe she's having a bad day, maybe she's in you know one of her hangry moods,
Quizás esté teniendo un mal día, quizás esté en una de sus fases hambrientas e irritables:
you don't let her emotions affect your emotions,
No dejes que sus sentimientos te influyan.
you are the peace in her storm, you are the rock.
Eres su roca, su pilar de apoyo.
Right, that's why that's why you often hear that cliche of mending the rock,
Es por esto que a menudo escuchamos el cliché "arreglar la piedra".
you have to be that emotional rock for her,
Tienes que ser esa roca emocional para ella.
and what happens when you employ emotional safety with woman.
¿Y qué pasa cuando le das seguridad emocional a una mujer?
is what you'll find is she starts to depend on you more,
Descubrirás que él confía más en ti.
she starts to open up to you more because you're not scary,
Ella se abre más a ti porque no la asustas.
she's not scared of how you're going to emotionally react,
Él no tiene miedo de tus reacciones emocionales.
this requires a high level of emotional intelligence from you,
Esto requiere un alto nivel de inteligencia emocional.
you have to be in command and control of your own emotions,
Debes tener control de tus emociones.
a certain bit of stoicism um in practicing this with women,
Una cierta calma estoica es esencial cuando se trata con mujeres.
but guys, i promise you when you can have and provide emotional safety,
Pero muchachos, les prometo: cuando irradian y ofrecen seguridad emocional,
emotional safety with yourself, but then provide emotional safety for her,
Primero la tuya, luego la seguridad que le puedes dar –
this unlocks a level of desire and attractiveness and
despertar un nuevo nivel de atracción y deseo. Y
really like this feeling of her just like wanting to be close to you that few
Me encanta esa sensación que tienes en ese momento, esa sensación de querer estar cerca de ti.
guys have ever experienced,
Los hombres ya lo saben,
because lot of women are scared to open up,
Porque muchas mujeres tienen miedo de abrirse,
lot of women aresca to be emotion emotionally vulnerable and to really just
Muchos se sienten emocionalmente vulnerables y lo necesitan desesperadamente.
be like their 100% real self with men because they don't feel emotionally safe,
Quieren ser completamente ellas mismas con los hombres porque no se sienten emocionalmente seguras.
so safety is the last aspect of desire.
Entonces, la seguridad es el último aspecto del deseo.
and attraction that men have to provide for women.
y la atracción que los hombres deben ofrecer a las mujeres.
so guys, that's it,
Bueno muchachos, eso es todo.
those are the five biggest aspects of desire attraction i see that you
Estos son los cinco aspectos más importantes de la atracción deseable. Los que deseas
have to embody if you want to have real success with the women you desire,
atraer
the women you actually want to attract in your life,
y con el que quieres tener éxito,
because she's going to require you to have these things.
Porque esperarán estas cualidades de ti.
so guys, that's it for day seven of the attraction blueprint guys,
¡Eso es todo por el séptimo día del Plan de Atracción!
i promise you this has been a quick course um,
Prometo que este curso fue corto y agradable…
but 'if you take each of these seven days to get better at them,
Pero si usas estos siete días para mejorar,
there's yes there's next levels to this and there's deeper
Sí, hay niveles aún más elevados y conocimientos más profundos.
work we can do um if you want to take that route just let us know,
Estaremos encantados de encargarnos de esto si te animas a emprender este viaje. Contáctanos.
but i promise you if you implement these seven days alone you will beat out 95%
Pero te prometo que si te comprometes con estos siete días, lo superarás.
of the other guys out there because they're simply just not doing these things
El 95% de los demás hombres, porque no hacen estas cosas en absoluto.
or they're just simply not good at them so get good at these seven days and
o simplemente no son buenos haciéndolos. Así que, practiquen diligentemente durante estos siete días y
i promise you it will absolutely transform your dating and relationship life
Prometo que transformará por completo tu vida amorosa y tus relaciones.
um buse you got to remember like this is not about just tracking me this
Um, Buse, recuerda, esto no se trata solo de acosarme. Se trata de...
keeping the woman right?
Quédate con la mujer, ¿verdad?
um, so this is something you're going to have to do from
Um, tienes que
the first date all the way through long-term relationship.
pasar de una primera cita a una relación a largo plazo.
um, so get better at these guys,
Umm, entonces trabaja en ti mismo con estos chicos.
let us know if you have any questions, stay in contact with us,
No dudes en contactarnos si tienes alguna pregunta, mantente en contacto.
we're here to help in any way that we can,
Estaremos encantados de ayudarle en todo lo que podamos.
and look, i would love to work with you further a deeper level,
Y escuchen, realmente me encantaría trabajar más intensamente con ustedes.
we do have one-on-one coaching, we do have next levels to this,
Ofrecemos coaching individual y también cursos avanzados.
so if that is something you're interested in let us know,
Si estás interesado, por favor ponte en contacto conmigo.
i would love to help you you know really accomplish all of your goals and dreams,
Estoy feliz de ayudarte a alcanzar tus metas y sueños.
that's what i'm here to do.
Por eso estoy aquí.
So thank you so much for spending this time with me today guys,
Muchas gracias por tomarte el tiempo para hablar conmigo hoy.
I really appreciate you and hopefully I will see you soon, bye guys!
Te lo agradezco mucho y espero verte pronto. ¡Adiós!